infozabout.com 2009-02-18

# Privacy Policy

At Our E-Book Software Package we are committed to protecting your privacy online. Our Privacy Policy demonstrates our firm commitment to protecting the privacy of our customers. We use the information that we collect about our customers to fulfill orders and to create a more personalized online experience.

At Our E-Book Software Package you can be assured that your transactional information is secure, consistent with current industry standard SSL encryption technology. The importance of security for all transactional information associated with our customers is of utmost concern to us. All customer transactional account information is kept on a secure server.

When you purchase the Our E-Book Software Package we collect transactional information and personally identifiable information from you, such as your name, telephone number, e-mail address, billing address, and credit card or other payment information. Our E-Book Software Package does not sell or rent your transactional information to others. Our E-Book Software Package uses customer information only for the purposes of order completion, contacting users to inform them of their order status, sending promotional information, and enhancing the user experience.

Credit Card information provided by the customer is used by Paypal, which handles Credit Card transactions on behalf of Our E-Book Software Package. Our E-Book Software Package can't obtain the customer?s Credit Card information from Paypal. Credit Card numbers are confidential between the customer and Paypal. For more information about Paypal and their Privacy Policy please visit their website at www.paypal.com 

Please be aware that our site may contain advertisements and links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. Information practices of those websites linking from or to our site are not covered by the Our E-Book Software Package Privacy Policy. Our E-Book Software Package has no control over the use or disclosure of user data on other sites on the Internet and we recommend that you review the privacy policies of such sites to determine your privacy rights on them. 

© 2009 - All Rights Reserved
